Need money? Get a Fiance...
My Fake Fiance is a tv movie, comedy, romance film directed by Gil Junger.
Jennifer and Vince, virtual strangers, find themselves strapped for cash and
decide to stage a fake engagement and wedding just for the gifts
Jennifer, played by Melissa Joan Hart.
Vince, played by Joey Lawrence.
Courtney, played by Nicole Tubiola.
Steve, played by Burgess Jenkins.
David, played by Jason MacDonald.
Bonnie, played by Diane Neal.
My Fake Fiancé is a 2009 American television film
starring Melissa Joan Hart and Joey Lawrence.
It premiered on the ABC Family channel on April 19, 2009.
The film explores themes of wedding, money problems, pretend relationship.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.